ROBERT GIFT OLUWASEUN

No 8, Amos Babarinde Folarin Street Alimosho

Telephone: 08032233306 **Email**: robertoluwaseunn@gmail.com

PROFILE

Self-motivated Customer Service Representative with over 2years of experience in managing customers with clear and transparent interaction. Strong communication skills that allow me to listen to a customer's problem and suggest acceptable solutions Dedication to keeping my skills and knowledge up to speed by learning new computer software working with innovative customer service approaches and being part of a team of knowledgeable colleagues.

EDUCATION

• Landmark University Omu-Aran Kawra State Bachelor of Science (Hon) Biochemistry.

2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Blue Mart Reality Ltd
Customer Service Representative

February 2023 till Date

Responsibilities

. Managed incoming customer inquiries via phone, email, and social media channels.

Provided product and service information to customers.

. Responded to customer complaints and resolve issues in a timely and effective manner. .

Processed customer orders and returns.

. Collaborated with other teams to ensure customer satisfaction.

Achievement

. Successfully built a sustainable relationship with customers, going the extra mile in all conversations.

• Oyo Mineral Development Agency

February 2022 to February 2023

Administrative Assistant - NYSC

Responsibilities

- . Developed and maintained a filing system.
- . Updated and maintained office policies and procedures.
- . Planned, coordinated, and managed all administrative procedures and systems. .

Performed other related duties as assigned.

Achievement

. Provided exceptional administrative support to managers and co-workers, increasing the overall efficiency of the office by 30%.

• Rmo Collections

September 2020 to January 2022

Customer Service Representative

Responsibilities

- . Assisted customers with their queries, concerns, and requests, while maintaining a polite and professional demeanor.
- . Received incoming calls from customers and potential clients, answering their questions, and providing accurate information.
- . Identified and resolved customer issues or complaints effectively and efficiently.
 - Escalated complex or unresolved issues to supervisors or higher management when necessary.

Achievements

. Met all provided sales targeted, by providing customers with information on new products, and sealing deals.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Team lead, Cross-Departmental Collaboration

February 2023

 Collaborated with other departments such as sales, marketing, and product development, sharing customers insights and contributing to the improvement of product and service

Team lead, Group Project

November 2020

- Led a team of 4 members for a research project focused on investigating the enzymatic activity of a specific protein
- Assigned and delegated responsibilities to all of them

CERTIFICATION

 Jobberman Soft Skills Training ing Certification 2023 January

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Girls' Education Initiative – Non-profit Organization

September 2020

 Volunteered to help empower and support girl chid education across different location in Lagos State

SKILLS

Proficient in Computer applications; (MSWord,PowerPoint and Excel)

• Soft Skills: Good problem solving, well-honed communication, and interpersonal skills